Which is the way out?
哪条是出去的路
There's an area they don't allow us to go.
有一个他们禁止我们去的地方
If I was a guessing person,
让我猜的话
I'd guess that's the closest thing this place has to an exit.
那里一定就相当于这地方的出口
Wait. Someone's coming.
等等  有人来了
What's that sound?
那是什么声音
There's something inside.
里面有东西
These are daemons without humans.
这些都是没有人类的精灵
David.
大卫
Shay.
雪伊
Bridget.
布里奇特
These daemons belong to the children
这些精灵都属于那些
who've been taken and not come back.
被带走就再没回来的孩子
That's Billy.
那是比利
His daemon is gone.
他的精灵不见了
That means...
那意味着
-I'm sorry, Roger. -You knew?
-我很难过  罗杰  -你早就知道了
I found him.
我找到了他
Before he died.
在他死之前
He got out of here somehow.
他不知用什么办法逃出了这里
I helped him find his ma.
我帮他找到了他妈妈
Lyra...
莱拉
...if the daemons are alive, where are the children?
如果精灵还活着  那孩子们去哪了
Seven, eight, nine, ten...
七  八  九  十
One, two, three..
一  二  三
Was Billy like this?
比利也是这副样子吗
Yes.
是的
We can't end up here.
我们不能变成那样
The alarm's stopped.
警报停了
We have to get back.
我们得回去了
Lyra!
莱拉